PAUL. N. THOMAS

I am a software developer working productively in dynamic environments. Fluent in Javascript, Java, Dart, PYTHON, HTML, PHP and CSS. I have worked with Quasar framework for mobile development, Vue js for front-end web development. and Laravel & Django for backend development.

WORK HISTORY

Bellinksfinace Tabora— Software Developer

FEB 2023 - MAY 2023

 Developed Internal software systems for banking and loan managementremotely.

Conture Education Networking Initiative (CENI), —

Software Developer

Nov 2022 - JAN 2023

• Developed system for managing school results, advertising job vacancies for teachers, facilitating teacher transfers, and selling courses-remotely.

PROJECTS

Conturetz— school management sytem(https://conturetz.com)

System for managing school results, advertising job vacancies for teachers, facilitating teacher transfers, and selling courses

• Web-App is available on the address www.conturetz.com

Bellinksfinance — (Bellicksfinace)

Loan management system

Tanzalearn — (https://tanzalearn.com/)

E-learning platform that I developed for a colleague using my own PHP FRAMEWORK which is available here (https://github.com/Ombenitango/2F)

2F - Fast Framework - (https://github.com/Ombenitango/2F)

Is an MVC php framework that I developed with the mindset of developing web applications very fast. All you need is a composer installed and you're ready to go.

SKILLS

Programming languages:

Javascript, Java, PHP, Python, Dart, Objective-C, C#.

Tanzania
Dodoma
+255 627857470
+255 675753415
paulnkingwa34@gmail.com
JUNE 2023

Other skills:

Reviewing, coding standards, eclipse, Java frameworks, requirements gathering, software documentation and version control systems.

Databases: Postgre, MySQL, MongoDB, SQLlite3.

DevOps: Docker, Git and Github, Gradle build tool and Groovy.

Operating Systems: Linux, Windows and MacOS.

Frameworks and libraries:

Vue js, Quasar framework, Flutter, React Native, React, Firebase, Django, Springboot, Tailwind, Bootstrap css.

Tools: Figma, VSCode, Midjourney.

LANGUAGES

English (Fluent),

Swahili (Fluent)

Twende —

(https://github.com/Ombenitango/ Twende) An IA model that can be used to predict cost of an event.

Ttrader

(https://colab.research.google.com/drive/1mfDHnPMPG8FEcmtiFVaAP g2IAUtozHwl?usp=sharing)

An IA bot for trading stock markets with high accuracy.

EDUCATION

The University of Dodoma (UDOM)-Dodoma, Tanzania

OCT 2021 TO PRESENT

Bachelor of Science in Software Engineering

Sengerema, Mwanza: Sengerema High School

MAY 2021

High school education, Physics, Chemistry and Mathematics

ST. MARY's SEMINARY, Mwanza— Secondary School

NOVEMBER 2018

Secondary Education

Lumala English Medium Primary School, Mwanza – Primary school

SEPTEMBER 2013